Hula, Erich; Papers ger044
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 7; 174 file folders
  - United Nations, Undated (Box 23 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1-5)
  - United Nations Charter revisions, Undated (Box 23 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - United Nations Conference on International Organization, Undated (Box 23 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Undated (Box 23 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8-9)
  - U.S. territories, Undated (Box 23 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Vietnam, Undated (Box 23 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - War Powers Act, Undated (Box 23 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Warfare, modern, Undated (Box 23 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Watergate, Undated (Box 23 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - World Court, Undated (Box 23 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Yugoslavia, Undated (Box 23 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
- Pamphlets, 8; 378 file folders
  This series of pamphlets deals predominantly with the United Nations and issues surrounding the United Nations.
  - A Design for a Charter of the General International Organization Envisioned in the Four-Nation Declaration of October 30, 1943 and in the Senate Resolution of November 5, 1943 (Tentative Draft), 1944 May 30 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 1)
  - A Design for a Charter of the General International Organization, Envisioned in the Moscow Declaration of October 30, 1943 and in the Resolution adopted by the Senate of the United States on November 5, 1943, 1944 August 01 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 2)
  - A Positive Policy Towards the United Nations.Recent Ministerial Statements of United Kingdom Policy, 1965 June (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 3)
  - A Positive Policy Towards the United Nations. Volume II. Statements of United Kingdom Policy June-December, 1965, Undated (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 4)
  - An Argument That Man Is Free, 1948 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 5)
  - Austrian Writers in the United States 1938-1968. An Exhibition of the Austrian Institute and the Austrian Forum, Inc., 1968 April (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 6)
  - The British Commonwealth and Empire, 1944 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 7)
  - British North America Act, 1949; Undated (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 8)
  - The Cameroons under French Administration. Text of Trusteeship Agreement as Approved by the General Assembly of the United Nations. New York, 13th December, 1946. Treaty Series No. 66, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 9)
  - Cameroons under United Kingdom Trusteeship. Text of Trusteeship Agreement as Approved by the General Assembly of the United Nations. New York, 13th December, 1946. Treaty Series No. 20, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 10)
  - Co-determination: How labor shares in German industry, ca. 1972 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 11)
  - Complaint to the Commission on Human Rights of the United Nations Concerning Violations of Human Rights Since the Erection of the Berlin Wall, 1962 September 25 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 12)
  - The Constitution of Norway. Foreword by Professor Dr. Wilhelm Keilhau, Undated (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 13)
  - Constitution of The United States of Brazil with the Constitutional Laws Nos. 1, 2, 3 and 4, 1941 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 14)
  - Decisions of the Central Committee, C.P.S.U.(B.) on Literature and Art (1946-1948), 1951 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 15)
  - The Declaration of Washington. February 1, 1956. A Joint Declaration of the President of the United States and the Prime Minister of the United Kingdom (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 16)
  - Declarations made to the Secretary-General of the United Nations by the Government of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland concerning the Optional Clause of the Statute of the International Court of Justice. New York, April 12 and 18, 1957 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 17)
  - Documents on the Korean Crisis, 1951 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 18)
  - Draft Constitution of the United States of Europe, 1944 April (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 19)
  - Draft Trusteeship Agreement for the Japanese Mandated Islands, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 20)
  - The Electoral System of the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics. A Collection of Official Documents, 1945 October 20 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 21)
  - Les Fédérations syndicales en Autriche, Undated 1937 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 22)
  - Germany. Facts and Figures About the Two German States. A Comparative Study, 1973 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 23)
  - Die Gewerkschaften in Österreich, Undated 1937 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 24)
  - History of Parliament. Register of the Ministers and of the Members of Both Houses 1439-1509, 1938 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 25)
  - Human Rights and Genocide. Selected Statements, United Nations Resolutions, September 21-December 12, 1948, 1949 February (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 26)
  - Imperial Conference, 1926. Summary of Proceedings (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 27)
  - Jamaica Constitution. Despatch from the Secretary of State for the Colonies to the Governor of Jamaica, dated 10th February, 1943, 1945 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 28)
  - Kann und soll die Schweiz den Vereinigten Nationen beitreten? Eine Diskussion in der "Neuen Zürcher Zeitung", 1966 February (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 29)
  - NATO. North Atlantic Treaty Organization. Its Development and Significance, 1955 September (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 30)
  - Nauru. Text of Trusteeship Agreement as Approved by the General Assembly of the United Nations, New York; 1st November, 1947. Treaty Series No. 89 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 31)
  - New Guinea. Text of Trusteeship Agreement as Approved by the General Assembly of the United Nations, New York, 13th December 1946. Treaty Series No. 68, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 32)
  - Pacific Islands. Text of Trusteeship Agreement as Approved by the Security Council of the United Nations, New York, 2nd April 1947. Treaty Series No. 76 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 33)
  - Portugal. Eight Centuries of History, 1940 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 34)
  - Portugal. The New State in Theory and in Practice, 1938 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 35)
  - Probleme der Verfolgung und Ahndung von nationalsozialistischen Gewaltverbrechen, 1967 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 36)
  - Revision of the United Nations Charter. Report of the Committee on Foreign Relations on Resolutions Relative to Revision of the United Nations Charter, Atlantic Union, World Federation, and Similar Proposals, 1950 September 01 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 37)
  - Ruanda-Urundi. Text of Trusteeship Agreement as Approved by the General Assembly of the United Nations, New York, 13th December, 1946. Treaty Series No. 64, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 38)
  - The Soviet White Paper on the North Atlantic Pact, 1949 March (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 39)
  - Statut de l'agence internationale de l'énergie atomique, 1956 November 01 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 40)
  - Statuto Fondamentale del Regno D'Italia promulgato nella Lombardia il giorno 7 decembre 1859, 1933 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 41)
  - Suggestions presented by The Netherlands Government Concerning the Proposals for the Maintenance of Peace and Security Agreed on at The Four Powers Conference of Dumbarton Oaks as Published on October 9, 1944, 1945 January (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 42)
  - Tanganyika. Text of Trusteeship Agreement as Approved by the General Assembly of the United Nations, New York, 13th December, 1946. Treaty Series No. 19, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 43)
  - Togoland under French Administration. Text of Trusteeship Agreement as Approved by the General Assembly of the United Nations, New York, 13th December, 1946. Treaty Series No. 67, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 44)
  - Togoland under United Kingdom Trusteeship. Text of Trusteeship Agreement as Approved by the General Assembly of the United Nations, New York, 13th December, 1946. Treaty Series No. 21, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 45)
  - Trade Union Organization in Austria, Undated 1937 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 46)
  - The Treaties of 1778, Undated (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 47)
  - Treaty of Economic, Social and Cultural Collaboration and Collective Self-Defence ... Brussels, 17th March, 1948. Treaty Series No. 1, 1949 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 48)
  - Trusteeship. Togoland and the Cameroons under United Kingdom Mandate, 1946 July (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 49)
  - United Kingdom Draft of An International Bill of Human Rights, 1947 June (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 50)
  - Western Samoa. Text of Trusteeship Agreement as Approved by the General Assembly of the United Nations (with Appendix), New York, 13th December, 1946. Treaty Series No. 65, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 51)
  - Ambassade de France.Constructive Action of the French Government in Algeria, 1957 January (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 52)
  - Ambassade de France.President DeGaulle Holds Fourth Press Conference, 1961 April 11 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 53)
  - American Bar Association.Report of Committee for Peace and Law Through United Nations, 1950 September 01 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 54)
  - American Society of International Law / American Political Science Association.A Survey of the Teaching of International Law in Political Science Departments, 1963 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 55)
  - The American Society of International Law.Teaching of International Law and Related Courses in American Law Schools, 1964 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 56)
  - Aronson, Gregor.Soviet Russia and the Jews, 1949 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 57)
  - Aufricht, Hans.The Fund Agreement: Living Law and Emerging Practice, 1969 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 58)
  - Bailey, Sydney D.Constitutions of the British Colonies, 1950 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 59)
  - Barnard, Chester I. et al.A Report on the International Control of Atomic Energy, 1946 March 16 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 60)
  - Barth, Frank.The Lost Peace. A Chronology: The League of Nations and the United States Senate 1918-1921, 1945 March (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 61)
  - Baruch, Bernard M.Proposals for an International Atomic Development Authority, 1946 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 62)
  - Berger, Peter.The Internationalization of Jerusalem, 1950 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 63)
  - Boggs, Marion William.Regulation and Reduction of Armaments. Action of the General Assembly, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 64)
  - Bogolepov, M. I.The Soviet Financial System. What it is and how it works, 1945 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 65)
  - Bolles, Blair.Who Makes Our Foreign Policy?, 1947 March-1947 April (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 66)
  - British Information Services.Britain and the United Nations, 1962 March (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 67)
  - British Information Services.Britain and the United Nations, 1964 November (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 68)
  - Budish, J. M.The Jewish Autonomous Region - Birobidjan, Undated (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 69)
  - Bundesministerium für innerdeutsche Beziehungen.Politik für Deutschland, 1970 September (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 70)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace.The Budget of the United Nations, 1947 September (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 71)
  - The Catholic Association for International Peace.Judging the Dumbarton Oaks Proposals. A Preliminary Statement of the Post War World Committee, Undated (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 72)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions.Religion. Interviews by Donald McDonald with Robert E. Fitch, John J. Wright, Louis Finkelstein, 1963 January (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 73)
  - Chagla, Mahomedali Currim.Kashmir. Text of Speeches by M.C.C., Union Minister of Education and Leader of the Indian Delegation, in the Security Council on February 5 & 10, 1964, 1964 March 31 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 74)
  - Chagla, Mahomedali Currim.Text of Speeches by M.C.C., Union Minister of Education and Leader of the Indian Delegation, in the Security Council on 7, 12, and 18 May 1964, 1964 May 30 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 75)
  - Clarke, R.W.B.Britain's Blockade, 1940 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 76)
  - Clubb, O. Edmund and Eustace Seligman.The International Position of Communist China, 1965 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 77)
  - Commission of the European Communities.Report on European Union, 1975 June 25 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 78)
  - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace.A Universal United Nations, 1962 July (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 79)
  - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace.International Bill of Human Rights, Undated (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 80)
  - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace.The United Nations and Non-Self Governing Peoples. A Plan for Trusteeship, 1944 December (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 81)
  - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace.The United Nations: The Next Twenty-Five Years, 1969 November (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 82)
  - Conant, James B.Our New Partner - The Federal Republic of Germany, 1955 June (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 83)
  - Conference of Lawyers of the Americas.World Peace Through the Rule of Law, 1961 June (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 84)
  - Cooke, Morris Llewellyn.Nasser's High Aswan Dam. Panacea or Politics?, ca. 1956 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 85)
  - Corwin, Edward S.The Will to Believe and S.J. Res. 1, 1954 January 26 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 86)
  - Coudenhove-Kalergi, R.N.Das pan-europäische Manifest, 1924 April (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 87)
  - Coudenhove-Kalergi, Richard.Toward a Constituant Assembly for Europe, Undated (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 88)
  - The Council on Religion and International Affairs.The Moral Dilemma of Nuclear Weapons, 1961 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 89)
  - Cushman, Robert E.Safeguarding Our Civil Liberties, 1940 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 90)
  - Cushman, Robert E.The Supreme Court and the Constitution, 1936 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 91)
  - Day, Brigham.Should the U.N. Charter Be Changed?, 1955 January (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 92)
  - Dayal, Ambassador Rajeshwar.First Progress Report to the Secretary-General from His Special Representative in the Congo, 1960 September 21 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 93)
  - de Lanux, Pierre.La Neutralité Américaine en 1936 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 94)
  - Dean, Arthur H.Excerpts from "Amending the Treaty Power", 1954 March 05 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 95)
  - The Department of State.A Report on the International Control of Atomic Energy, 1946 March 16 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 96)
  - The Department of State.Atomic Energy and Conventional Armaments. Selected Statements United Nations Resolutions. September 21-December 12, 1948, 1949 February (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 97)
  - Department of State.The Bangkok Conference of the Manila Pact Powers. February 23-25, 1955, 1955 August (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 98)
  - Department of State.The Economic and Social Council of the United Nations, 1946 July 15 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 99)
  - Department of State.80th Congress and the United Nations, 1948 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 100)
  - Department of State.Eightieth Congress First Session and the United Nations, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 101)
  - The Department of State.The International Control of Atomic Energy. Scientific Information transmitted to the United Nations Atomic Energy Commission. December 15, 1946, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 102)
  - The Department of State.The International Control of Atomic Energy. The First Report of the United Nations Atomic Energy Commission to the Security Council, December 31, 1946, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 103)
  - The Department of State.The International Control of Atomic Energy. The Second Report of the United Nations Atomic Energy Commission to the Security Council, September 11, 1947, 1947 December (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 104)
  - The Department of State.The International Control of Atomic Energy. The Third Report of the United Nations Atomic Energy Commission to the Security Council, May 17, 1948, 1948 July (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 105)
  - Department of State.Korea's Independence, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 106)
  - Department of State.NATO. North Atlantic Treaty Organization. Its Development and Significance, 1952 August (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 107)
  - Department of State.The North Atlantic Pact. Collective Defense and the Preservation of Peace, Security, and Freedom in the North Atlantic Community, 1949 March (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 108)
  - Department of State.North Atlantic Treaty. Proposed for Signature during First Week in April, 1949, 1949 March (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 109)
  - The Department of State.Nine-Power Conference. London, September 28-October 3, 1954, 1954 October (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 110)
  - The Department of State.Peaceful Uses of Atomic Energy, 1955 June (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 111)
  - The Department of State.The Problem of Peace in Korea, an oral report by Secretary of State Dean Acheson, October 24, 1952, 1952 October (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 112)
  - Department of State.Report of the United States Delegates to the United Nations Conference on Freedom of Information. Geneva, Switzerland, March 23-April 21, 1948 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 113)
  - Department of State.Southeast Asia Treaty Organization. First Annual Report of the Council Representatives, 1956 March (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 114)
  - The Department of State.Toward a Stronger United Nations, 1948 December (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 115)
  - The Department of State.Treaty of Peace with Japan, signed at San Francisco, September 8, 1951. With Related Documents, 1952 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 116)
  - The Department of State.Trial of Japanese War Criminals. Documents, 1946 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 117)
  - The Department of State.United Nations Action in Korea Under Unified Command. Second Report to the Security Council, August 16, 1950 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 118)
  - The Department of State.United Nations Action in Korea Under Unified Command. Fourth Report to the Security Council, September 17, 1950 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 119)
  - The Department of State.United Nations Action in Korea Under Unified Command. Fifth Report to the Security Council, October 5, 1950 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 120)
  - The Department of State.United Nations Action in Korea Under Unified Command. Sixth Report to the Security Council, October 21, 1950 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 121)
  - The Department of State.United Nations Action in Korea Under Unified Command. Seventh Report to the Security Council, November 3, 1950 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 122)
  - The Department of State.United Nations Action in Korea Under Unified Command. Eighth, Ninth, and Tenth Reports to the Security Council, 1950 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 123)
  - The Department of State.United Nations Action in Korea Under Unified Command. Eleventh Report to the Security Council, January 31, 1951 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 124)
  - The Department of State.The United Nations and the Problem of Greece, 1947 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 125)
  - Department of State.The United States and Non-Self-Governing Territories, 1947 April 05 (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 126)
  - The Department of State.United States Policy in the Korean Conflict, July 1950-February 1951, 1951 September (Box 24 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 127)
  - Dodd, Thomas J.Is the United Nations Worth Saving?, 1962 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 1)
  - Dulles, John Foster.Intervention! The Story of International Communism in the Americas, 1954 March 08 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 2)
  - Dulles, John Foster.Report on Asia - March 1956, 1956 March 23 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 3)
  - Dulles, John Foster.The Spirit of the United Nations, 1955 June 24 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 4)
  - Dulles, John Foster.The Suez Problem, 1956 October 09 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 5)
  - Dulles, John Foster.Text of Speech by J.F.D. Secretary of State Before the Tenth Inter-American Conference, Caracas, Venezuela, March 4, 1954, (Press Release No. 109), Undated (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 6)
  - Eichelberger, Clark M.The United Nations Charter. What Was Done at San Francisco, 1945 July (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 7)
  - Elder, Robert E. and Forrest D. Murden.Economic Co-operation. Special United Nations Fund for Economic Development (SUNFED), 1954 September (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 8)
  - Elliott, Mabel A.Coercion in Penal Treatment: Past and Present, 1947 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 9)
  - Eppstein, John.Defend these Human Rights, Undated (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 10)
  - Eppstein, John."One World". What Kind do Catholics Want? The Christian Tradition in International Relations, 1944 December (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 11)
  - Epstein, William.Retrospective on the NPT Review Conference: Proposals for the Future, 1975 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 12)
  - Farmer, Fyke.Plan for Representation in World Constituent Assembly at Geneva, 1950, Undated (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 13)
  - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America.The Christian Conscience and Weapons of Mass Destruction, 1950 December (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 14)
  - Freeman, Harrop.Coercion of States in International Organizations, 1944 April (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 15)
  - Freeman, Harrop and Theodore Paullin.Coercion of States: In Federal Unions, 1943 January (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 16)
  - Freeman, Harrop A. and Theodore Paullin.Road to Peace. A Study in Functional International Organization, 1947 March (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 17)
  - German Information Center.Federal Republic of Germany: Elections / Parliament and Political Parties, 1976 May (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 18)
  - German Information Center.The Federal Republic of Germany Salutes the United States of America on its 200th Anniversary, 1976 April (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 19)
  - Ginsberg, Morris.Nationalism. A Reappraisal, 1961 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 20)
  - Goodhart, A.L.The British Constitution, 1943 May (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 21)
  - Graham, Robert A. and Robert C. Hartnett. Ed. Charles Keenan. Diplomatic Relations with the Vatican, 1952 January 15 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 22)
  - Gromyko, Andrei.A Speech by Andrei Gromyko, Soviet Delegate to the UN on A Palestine Solution, 1947 May 14 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 23)
  - Gross, Leo.Bulgaria Invokes The Connally Amendment, 1962 April (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 24)
  - Gross, Leo.Domestic Jurisdiction, Enforcement Measures and the Congo, 1966 December (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 25)
  - Gross, Leo.Expenses of the United Nations for Peace-Keeping Operations: The Advisory Opinion of the International Court of Justice, 1963 May (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 26)
  - Gross, Leo.Immunities and Privileges of Delegations to the United Nations, 1962 October (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 27)
  - Gross, Leo.International Law and Peace, 1968 April (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 28)
  - Gross, Leo.The Jurisprudence of the World Court, 1964 January (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 29)
  - Gross, Leo.Limitations upon the Judicial Function, 1964 May (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 30)
  - Gross, Leo.Passage Through the Strait of Tiran and in the Gulf of Agaba, 1968 November (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 31)
  - Gross, Leo.Some Observations on the International Court of Justice, 1962 January (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 32)
  - Gross, Leo.The United Nations and the Role of Law, 1965 November (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 33)
  - Gross, Leo.United Nations - Coalition or World Society, 1943 February (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 34)